# BRANDT KELLER

11504 21<sup>st</sup> PL NE, Lake Stevens, WA 98258 · (425)-219-2289 · Info@Brandtkeller.net https://www.linkedin.com/in/brandtkeller - Brandtkeller.net - https://github.com/brandt-keller

Full stack Software Engineer with experience building RESTful microservices and User Interfaces. Working closely with product managers to define, meet, and engineer customer requirements. Willing to learn and adapt to new technologies. U.S. Marine of 5 years in a Technical and Leadership Role with a Secret security clearance.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SEPTEMBER 2018 – CURRENT**

## JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER, STRATAGEN SYSTEMS

Software Development Engineer, building enterprise application software User Interface in EmberJS. Utilizing AWS cloud infrastructure, Jenkins CI/CD pipelines, REST API's, websocket data ingestion, and PostgreSQL. Contributing to integration with legacy systems while transitioning to latest release.

#### MARCH 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

#### **SDET INTERN, STRATAGEN SYSTEMS**

Quality assurance and testing intern, developing automated testing suites using Docker and Axios for software releases. Built unit, integration and system testing for backend services and User Interface end-to-end, including realistic dataset creation in SQL. Integrated tests into CI/CD processes to ensure quality of new changes.

#### **JANUARY 2016 - MARCH 2018**

### **ASSEMBLY, BUCHANAN AUTOMATION**

Assembly, diagnostics and modification of industrial pneumatic and electrical automation equipment in order to facilitate the needs of the client. Ensured quality assurance of all assemblies prior to their departure.

#### SEPTEMBER 2010 - SEPTEMBER 2015

## **SERGEANT, U.S. MARINE CORPS**

Communications Chief, Blackfoot Company, 3d Light Armored Reconnaissance Battalion. Tested, programmed, and integrated newly awarded DOD contract for vehicular communications system. Awarded Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal, August 2012 in Southern-Helmand Province, Afghanistan.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **AUGUST 2018**

#### BS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON BOTHELL

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Software Engineering with emphasis in Information Assurance and Cybersecurity. 3.5 Cumulative GPA.

#### SKILLS

- Strong knowledge of C++, C#, Java and JavaScript.
- Jenkins CI/CD DevOps utilization

- Cloud services and infrastructure
- GIT workflow

I enjoy working as a team to collaborate, share ideas, and work to improve the skillset of the entire team. Quality of work and initiative are important to my work ethic in accomplishing the task, while proposing or making enhancements where possible.